

# **Artem Lisovik**

## Front end developer (React)

Kyiv, Ukraine

## **Socials**

- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/artem-lisovyk-511072192
- Artemlisovik@icloud.com
- **2** +38-073-17-333-57
- https://artemlisovik.github.io/portfolio/

## Hard skills:

- HTML/CSS (SASS)
- JavaScript (ES6+)
- Typescript
- React
- Redux
- Firebase
- Responsive design
- WebPack / GULP
- Mentoring ability

## Soft skills:

- Great communications
- Problem-solving
- Organizational
- Responsible
- Self-taught
- Proactive

#### **ABOUT**

I'm front-end developer with over 2 year of commercial experience in creating and optimizing web applications. I have experience in creating MVP projects, long-term support, bug fixes and transfer projects to the new technologies.

I'm looking for a challenging tasks, friendly work environment and possibility to learn new technologies and career growth.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Freelance**

Work period: 03.06.2021 - now

- Creating responsive multipage websites (html5/css3(scss), VanilaJS (no frameworks/ libraries), gulp)
- Creating/server SPA using React
- Improve loading speed existed projects and bug fixes (lazy, code cleaning, source unification)!
- Personal mentoring

## Baldinini/Lagerfeld offline store director

Work period: 03.06.2019 - 15.03.2023

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

#### Front end developer

Self-taught

Years of Graduation: 2021 - now

Kyiv, Ukraine

Finished a few courses (udemy), self research

## **Bachelor Mechanic Engineer**

Institution: National Transport University

Years of Graduation: 2012 - 2016

Kyiv, Ukraine